Mohammad AbuDayeh

Website: https://abudayeh.me
Phone: +962 785685087
Email: e@hotmail.com

Profile

Security researcher specialized in finding web applications vulnerabilities, He has over 9 years of experience in information security field that varies from Web Application Security, Incident handling and Network Security with a good knowledge of Web Applications Development.

Achievements

Discover many critical vulnerabilities in Microsoft corporate systems. And discover security holes in government sectors and special.

Education

Bachelor Degree of Software engineering University of Islamic Sciences.

2016 - 2019

Experience

Cyber security, English language, Soft Skills Al Hussein Technical University, National ICT Up-Skilling Programme.

Feb - Present, 2020

Cyber Security Certification

Cisco Networking.

CNSS | Certified Network Security Specialist

2019 - 2020

2018 - 2019

ICIS.

Autopsy Basics and Hands Autopsy Digital Forensics.

2017 - 2020

Full Stack Development Track

1 Million Jordanian Coders.

2019 - 2020

Skills

Professional: Respond to cyber attacks, Penetration analysis, Check

vulnerabilities, Protecting the network.

Personal: Communication, Creativity, Dedication, Teamwork.

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux, macOS.

Programming: PHP, Python, SQL, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap.

Projects

Control Panel app: I worked during the graduation project with 4 other colleagues to develop PHP and MySQL database.